# The following questions are from the Open Trivia Database (https://opentdb.com/):

question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "St. Louis is the capital of the US State Missouri.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "California is larger than Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Vatican City is a country.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]